

# Pejman Kiamehr

## Front-End Developer (React, Next. js)

### Summary

I am a React Developer with over several year of experience in building websites and organizational panels. Having a solid foundation in responsive design, experience collaborating with back-end and APIs, and familiarity with SEO principles, I am eager to expand my skills and contribute as part of a dynamic front-end development team. Portfolio (www.kiamehr.dev).

#### Contact Information

**→** Phone +98 915 550 3369

Mobile

Email kiamehr.dev@gmail.com

#### Portfolio

Website https://www.kiamehr.dev

Personal Portfolio

GitHub https://github.com/pejmankiamehr

#### Technical Skills

- Frontend Development HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript, React.js, Next.js

  - Styling / UI Tailwind CSS, Material UI, React Bootstrap, Responsive Design, Media Queries

State/API • Redux Toolkit, Context API, Zustand, RESTful APIs, Axios, Postman

Version/Deploy • Git, GitHub, GitLab, Vercel, figma

Tools • npm, Vite.js, Postman, Figma

# Professional Experiences

2024 Freelance Front-end Developer (React, Next.js), mashhad.

Designed responsive UIs, optimized performance, and deployed projects on GitHub and Vercel.

2023–2024 **Webmaster** — **BrandingPro**, *mashhad*.

 Maintained and updated company website. Implemented basic SEO optimizations and responsive design fixes. Managed content and coordinated with design team.

2022-2023 Technical Support (Web/Server)—Green web (Iran Server), mashhad.

• Provided web/server support for corporate clients in a large-scale hosting company.

2021–2022 Junior Front-end Developer (React) — Eight Team, mashhad.

• Developing responsive user interfaces with React and UI libraries, collaborating with the back-end team.

2018–2020 Technical Support Specialist—Snap Team( Romak Holding, Tehran.

Supported operational systems, troubleshooting issues in a fast-paced team environment.

# Education/Certificates

2019–2020 Web Package Design(Web1, Web2, Web3), Tehran Institute of Technology, Tehran.

Received a certificate from Tehran Institute of Technology for completing courses in web development.

2009–2013 B.Sc. in Mechanical Engineering, Islamic Azad University, Mashhad.

Received a Bachelor's degree in Mechanical Engineering from Islamic Azad University.

#### Soft Skills

Strong team player with a collaborative mindset, excellent written and verbal communication skills, and outstanding presentation and negotiation abilities.